To make us understand that,
evil deeds are followed by
evil repercussions.
And good deeds are followed
by goodness.
If you are upon good deeds,
if a person is upon sin,
he begins to anticipate
khairat,
barakat.
The day he starts tawbah.
He will feel it by himself.
I have turned a new leaf.
And I know somebody who was
like
that.
He used to be on drugs.
He is late now.
He used to have people.
He would be in bus stops,
pickpockets.
All of this.
Their house is just about 5
or
6 houses away from us.
And his father was well
known.
This boy just turned one day.
He observed salah.
He went to the masjid.
The masjid where if he came,
everybody was afraid what he
came to
do.
He made wudu, two units of
prayer.
Just like that.
This boy turned.
Muhammad was his name.
He turned.
He began upon good deeds.
So that time, everybody who
saw him,
they said,
We are looking calm now.
We are looking honorable.
We are looking this.
One of the men in the masjid
volunteered